linkdsl.com 2011-05-26

# Welcome to LINKDSL - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is as important to us as it is to you. We're committed to protecting your personal information while enabling you to benefit from the useful, convenient features offered on the LINKdotNET web site. To serve you more efficiently and effectively, we sometimes collect personal information.

For example, we automatically record your IP address so we can establish a broad understanding of site traffic patterns. It also helps us diagnose server problems and perform site administration. Also, we use "cookies" to gather information about your preferences as you navigate through the site. This helps us tailor and improve the information we present to you, so you enjoy an exceptional customer experience every time you visit. 

In addition, our online ordering process requests your contact information, such as your address, telephone number and email address. In combination, your address and telephone number are the only way we can determine the type of DSL service and speed we can provide to you. We use your email address to send confirmation notices and updates when you request information for LINKdotNET services. If you have submitted your information more than one time, it is likely that you will be contacted separately for each submittal. 

We have established multiple security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of any information under our control. We do not sell personal information to third parties. We will, however, share personal information if we are required by law or, subject to your consent, where a particular service requiring such disclosure is requested by you. 

Please note that our web site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the content of these sites. If you have questions about this privacy statement or the LINKdotNET web site practices, please contact us
